export const questions = [
    {id: 1,
        question: "What Array property in Python is used to add an item in array?",
        options: ["array.pop(item)",
            "array.add(item)",
            "array.append(item)",
            "array.shift(item)"
        ],
        answer: "array.append(item)"
    },

    {id: 2,
        question: "Which Python Library is used to create a data structure?",
        options: ["numpy",
            "matplotlib",
            "pandas",
            "scikit-learn"
        ],
        answer: "pandas"
    },

    {id: 3,
        question: "Which of following is a classification technique?",
        options: ["linear regression",
            "logistic regression",
            "k nearest neighbour",
            "tensorflow"
        ],
        answer: "k nearest neighbour"
    },

    {id: 4,
        question: "which of the following is a unsupervised learniing technique?",
        options: ["support vector classifier",
            "logistic regression",
            "k nearest neighbour",
            "clustering"
        ],
        answer: "clustering"
    },

    {id: 5,
        question: "Which of these python libraries are used for computer vision problem solving?",
        options: ["scikit-learn",
            "numpy",
            "pandas",
            "openCV"
        ],
        answer: "openCV"
    },
    {id: 6,
        question: "Which of following python library is not used for deep learning?",
        options: ["Tensorflow",
            "Pytorch",
            "scikit-learn",
            "Keras"
        ],
        answer: "scikit-learn"
    },

    {id: 7,
        question: "What command used to import an excel file in python",
        options: ["pandas.load_excel",
            "pandas.readExcel",
            "pandas.read_Excel",
            "pandas.read_excel"
        ],
        answer: "pandas.read_excel"
    },
    {id: 8,
        question: "Sigmoid function is used in which of the following machine learning technique?",
        options: ["k nearest neighbour",
            "logistic regression",
            "k mean clustering",
            "linear regression"
        ],
        answer: "logistic regression"
    },
    {id: 9,
        question: "which python library is used to construct arrays and matrices?",
        options: ["pandas",
            "numpy",
            "seaborn",
            "matplotlib"
        ],
        answer: "numpy"
    },

    {id: 10,
        question: "which of following is a unique attribute of unsupervised learning?",
        options: ["it can train model",
            "it can test model",
            "it trains data patterns to make predictions for automated decision making and forecasting",
            "it uses unlabelled data to train and test data models to build patterns for making predictions, forecasting and automated decision making"
        ],
        answer: "it uses unlabelled data to train and test data models to build patterns for making predictions, forecasting and automated decision making"
    },
    

]
